Wonderful.
素晴らしい｡
Where we left off is we had just created the Get Features function, which builds our features dictionary
この関数は､ 4つの機能を使って機能辞書を作成します｡
Let's look at one so we can call get features for let's say our initial training point.
例えば､ 最初のトレーニングポイントについて､ フィーチャーを呼び出すことができる｡
And what we get back is this nice little this little dictionary.
そして返ってくるのは､ この小さな小さな辞書だ｡
Apparently it's £2.2 in its weight.
どうやら2ポンドらしい｡  2の重さである｡
That's its average rank.
これが平均的な順位だ｡
That's the length of the text.
それが本文の長さだ｡
And it is not a top electronics brand.
しかも､ エレクトロニクスのトップブランドではない｡
So these become the rather meager features that we have engineered.
だから､ これらは私たちが設計したかなり貧弱な機能になる｡
You can do better and I challenge you to do so.
あなたならもっとうまくやれる｡
All right.
分かった｡
Now it's time for some machine learning.
さあ､ 機械学習の時間だ｡
There's this little utility function that's going to take a list of items and convert it into a dataframe.
この小さなユーティリティ関数は､ アイテムのリストを受け取ってデータフレームに変換する｡
A pandas dataframe.
パンダのデータフレーム｡
Not going to go through this in detail, because this is not a course about traditional machine learning.
これは伝統的な機械学習についてのコースではないので､ 詳しく説明するつもりはない｡
If you know DataFrames and you'll be familiar with this, and we use this to make a training dataframe
DataFramesをご存じであれば､ これはよくご存じだと思うが､ これを使ってトレーニング・データフレームとテスト・データフレームを作り､
and a test dataframe, just picking the top 250 points in our test data set.
テスト・データセットの上位250ポイントを選ぶ｡
So there we go.
そうだ｡
We've made our conversion and now this is the business.
転換を果たし､ 今はこれがビジネスだ｡
This is where we run traditional linear regression.
ここで伝統的な線形回帰を実行する｡
We set our features.
私たちは機能を設定した｡
Um we specify the names of the columns of our features.
ここで特徴量のカラム名を指定する｡
This is where all the action happens.
ここがすべてのアクションが起こる場所だ｡
Model equals linear regression is saying we want a linear regression model.
Model equals linear regressionは､ 線形回帰モデルが欲しいと言っている｡
And then we fit that model to our x values, our features and our y values is the actual prices of our
そして､ そのモデルをx値､ つまり特徴量に当てはめ､ y値をトレーニングデータセットの実際の価格に当てはめる｡
And that this this is where the action happens and where the model is actually fit.
そして､ ここがアクションが起こる場所であり､ モデルが実際にフィットする場所なのだ｡
Then going to print the the features and their coefficients or how much weight they got.
そして､ 特徴量とその係数､ あるいは重み付けを印刷する｡
So we can see that and get a sense of how important were each of our features.
そのため､ 各機能がどれだけ重要であったかを知ることができる｡
And then we will actually run a prediction on that test set and get things like the, the MSE, the
そして､ 実際にテスト・セットで予測を実行し､ MSE､
mean squared error and the r squared for for the data scientists amongst you that want to have a look
平均二乗誤差､ r二乗などを求めます｡
at that.
しかし､ 恐れることはない｡ 私たちが以前に構築したフレームワークを使って､ もちろんそれを見ることができるのだ｡
That's going to show it on the same graph.
それが同じグラフに表示される｡
So make your guess where you think this is going to come out compared to the average model.
だから､ 平均的なモデルと比較して､ これがどこに出てくると思うか､ 推測してみてほしい｡
Let's quickly look back at the average model to remind ourselves what we're trying to beat.
私たちが何を目指しているのかを思い出すために､ 平均的なモデルを簡単に振り返ってみよう｡
So an average guess has an error of 145 $146.
つまり､ 平均的な推測では145ドルの誤差がある｡
So hopefully linear regression can do better than average.
だから､ 線形回帰が平均よりも良い結果を出してくれることを願っている｡
Let's see.
見てみよう｡
Let's first run it.
まずは実行してみよう｡
It's quick.
早いよ｡
Uh, so the different uh, um coefficients, the weights that it gave things, you can see that how
つまり､ 係数や重みを変えてみると､ 重いものには小さな､
heavy something is gets a small uh, positive weight.
プラスの重みがつくことがわかる｡
How it ranks gets a larger one.
どのようにランク付けされるかは､ もっと大きなものだ｡
The text length is very small signal very low.
テキストの長さは非常に小さい｡
Is it a top electronics brand?
エレクトロニクスのトップブランドですか？
Makes a big difference.
大きな違いだ｡
Things that are top electronics brands get a lot.
エレクトロニクスのトップブランドは､ 多くのものを手に入れる｡
Um, okay, so now, uh, we simply wrap this in a function because this is what we're going to use
さて､ それでは､ クールなテスト・ヴィジュアライザーで使用するために､ この関数を単純にラップします｡
We wrap it in a function called linear regression Pricer.
これを線形回帰Pricerと呼ばれる関数で包む｡
And we will then just use we will it passes in an item.
そして､ 私たちはそれをアイテムに使うだけだ｡
We will get the features for that item.
私たちはそのアイテムの機能を取得します｡
We will then convert that to a data frame.
それをデータフレームに変換する｡
And then we will call our linear regression model to predict where that comes.
そして､ その結果を予測するために線形回帰モデルを呼び出す｡
And let's see what happens.
どうなるか見てみよう｡
Tester dot test.
テスターのドットテスト｡
Linear regression Pricer.
線形回帰 プライサー
Are you ready for this.
準備はできているか？
Remember what the average number was.
平均的な数字が何だったか覚えている？
Here we go.
さあ､ 始めよう｡
Oh, uh, execute the cell before.
あ､ あの､ 前の独房でやってください｡
Uh, how many times have I done that now?
ええと､ もう何度目だろう？
Bam!
バム！
Well, we can see the colors.
まあ､ 色は見える｡
We can see that it's got a lot of reds in there, but maybe some more greens than before.
赤が多いが､ 以前より緑が増えたかもしれない｡
Maybe it hasn't done terribly.
たぶん､ ひどい結果にはなっていない｡
It's getting some things right.
いくつかのことはうまくいっている｡
Let's see.
見てみよう｡
Well, there we have it.
まあ､ そういうことだ｡
It's only done a little bit better than the average.
平均より少し良くなった程度だ｡
Only a little bit better.
少し良くなっただけだ｡
And indeed if you look at the results you can see that basically there's a small increase here, but
そして､ その結果を見てみると､ 基本的にはわずかな上昇が見られるが､
it's clustered Stood around the average kind of point, with some of the points coming in about $200
平均的なポイントに集中しており､ 200ドルほど高いポイントもある｡
And guess what?
そして何だと思う？
Those are going to be the ones where is electronics brand is is is true is top electronics brand.
これらのブランドは､ エレクトロニクス・ブランドであり､ トップ・エレクトロニクス・ブランドである｡
Uh, and so they got a little uplift which did well for this one point here.
それで､ この1点に関しては､ 少し上昇した｡
But otherwise uh, didn't particularly work out well for the model.
でも､ それ以外は......モデルとしては特にうまくいかなかった｡
Uh, so it tried its best.
ベストを尽くした｡
It got a, uh, 139, um, uh, error.
139エラーが出たんだ｡
And it, it it had a hit.
そして､ ヒットした｡
It was green, uh, almost 16% of the time.
ほぼ16％の確率でグリーンだった｡
So that's our linear regression model.
これが線形回帰モデルだ｡
You can do better.
もっとうまくやれるはずだ｡
Come on in.
どうぞお入りください｡
Now, engineer some features.
では､ いくつかの機能を設計してみよう｡
I know it's not new.
今に始まったことではないのは分かっている｡
Uh, great.
ああ､ 素晴らしい｡
LM data science, but it's really good to build this foundational knowledge and doing some old school
LMのデータ・サイエンスは､ 基礎的な知識を築き､ 昔ながらのフィーチャー・エンジニアリングを行うのに適している｡
And besides, it's going to make it all the more satisfying when we start working with LMS and see how
それに､ LMSと一緒に仕事を始めて､ その成果を見ることができれば､ もっと満足できるだろう｡
So come on in there, build some features, see how you do.
だから､ そこに来て､ いくつかの機能を作って､ どうやるか見てみよう｡
But next time we're going to, uh, look at some more sophisticated baseline models.
でも次回は､ もう少し洗練されたベースラインモデルを見てみよう｡
I will see you then.
それではまた｡